voddler.com 2017-06-23

# Website Privacy Policy | Voddler Group

**Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy is very, very important to us. It is our principle not to share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law or protect our rights. We do not store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services. 

Voddler Group AB operates voddlergroup.com and its subdomains, including vnet.se and simulation.vnet.se. It is Voddler Group AB’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our web properties. 

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, Voddler Group AB collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Voddler Group’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Voddler Group AB’s visitors use its website. 

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to Voddler Group AB’s websites choose to interact with Voddler Group AB in ways that require Voddler Group to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Voddler Group AB gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who want to create a VoddlerNet user account to provide a name, email address and place of work. Voddler Group AB collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Voddler Group AB. Voddler Group AB does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
Voddler Group AB may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Voddler Group AB may monitor geographic spread of users who request to download our whitepapers. However, Voddler Group AB does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
Voddler Group AB discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Voddler Group AB’s behalf or to provide services available at Voddler Group AB’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Voddler Group AB’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Voddler Group AB will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Voddler Group AB discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Voddler Group AB believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Voddler Group AB, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Voddler Group AB website and have supplied your email address, Voddler Group AB may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Voddler Group AB and our products. We primarily use our web site and social media to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Voddler Group AB takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Voddler Group AB uses cookies to help Voddler Group AB identify and track visitors, their usage of Voddler Group AB website, and their website access preferences. Voddler Group AB visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Voddler Group AB’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Voddler Group AB’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfer**  
If Voddler Group AB, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Voddler Group AB goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Voddler Group AB may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Voddler Group AB may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Voddler Group AB’s sole discretion. Voddler Group AB encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

_Dated: 12 November 2015_
